### Hubungi

Komplek Eks Yon Angkub K2 No.2 RT 012 RW 002, Kelurahan Kramatjati, Kecamatan Kramatjati, Jakarta Timur. 08979501887 (Mobile) rivalmsayid@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rivalmuhammad-sayid-b07981228 (LinkedIn)

github.com/rivalmsayid (Personal) gitlab.com/rivalmsayid (Personal)

#### Keahlian Teratas

TestRail Bootstrap (Framework) HTML5

### Certifications

UNAS English Proficiency
Website Developer: E-commerce
Certificate Of Competency | Teknik
Komputer dan Jaringan

Certified Internasional Specialist Data Visualization

IT Support

# Rival Muhammad Sayid

Quality Assurance Engineer - Student at Binar Academy Jakarta Raya, Indonesia

## Ringkasan

Hi, I'm Rival Muhammad Sayid! Informatics graduate of 2022 with boundless passion for technology and quality. Currently, I am pursuing an interesting career journey in the professional world.

With a passion for continuous learning and growth, I am currently focusing on my role as a professional in the technology industry. I have a special interest in Quality Assurance (QA) and am currently actively participating in the Quality Assurance bootcamp program at Binar Academy. Through this program, I seek to deepen my understanding of software testing and product quality, as well as hone the technical skills needed to ensure a great user experience.

My experience in technology has given me valuable insight into how technological innovation and excellence can shape the future. Apart from academic experience, I also have practical experience in technology based projects which has equipped me with the ability to adapt quickly in a changing environment.

I enjoy collaborating and interacting with colleagues who share passion in presenting the best solutions. If you are interested in discussing technology, software quality, or other collaboration opportunities, please feel free to contact me.

## Pengalaman

PASIFIK SATELIT NUSANTARA Helpdesk Support Maret 2022 - Present (1 tahun 6 bulan) Jakarta Selatan, Jakarta Raya, Indonesia

AKBAR MANDIRI PERKASA Web Developer Juni 2022 - Juli 2022 (2 bulan) JI. Pamikul 3 No.26, RT.04/RW.06, Tegal Gundil, Kec. Bogor Utara, Kota Bogor

Projek Membuat Website Company Profile

PT. Unibless Indo Multi Data Entry Operator September 2021 - Februari 2022 (6 bulan)

Jakarta Selatan, Jakarta Raya, Indonesia

Unibless Indo Multi IT Support Technician Juni 2021 - Juli 2021 (2 bulan)

Grand Ps. Minggu, Ruko, Jl. Raya Rw. Bambu No.88, RT.13/RW.5, Ps. Minggu, Kec. Ps. Minggu, Jakarta.

- Instalasi Komputer
- Instalasi Perangkat Lunak (Operating System & Aplikasi)
- Maintenance Komputer
- Troubleshooting Komputer
- Maintenance Printer

### Pendidikan

**Binar Academy** 

QAE, Quality Assurance Engineer · (Juni 2023 - Oktober 2023)

Universitas Nasional (UNAS)

Gelar Sarjana, Informatika · (November 2018 - November 2022)